

The Digital Artist's Résumé

Email: <u>kironroydev@outlook.com</u>

Portfolio: <u>https://kironroy.github.io/</u>

Phone: (562).221.3248

About Me

I am a digital artist that loves to problem solve and communicate with different types of people. A life long learner, my C# and Excel skills have trained me to think analytically and my job experience contributed to my people skills.

Work Experience

Census 2020 Enumerator

Department of Commerce - Orange County, CA

August 2020 - August 2020,

Interview residents at their homes for the Census 2020 and enter their interview questions into an iPhone app.

Bookkeeper

Rita Roy Pediatrics

October 2010 - Present (Telecommunicate)

Bookkeeping with Excel.

Billing/Posting payments to Office Ally.

Payroll taxes for two employees with EFTPS.

Billing Information Ruby Language.

Rita Page Vue JavaScript Framework.

Front-end web services

Om Imports

July 2011 - August 2012, July 2018 - November 2018

Product Photography. Editing photographs with Photoshop and updating the company website: Om Imports.

Accounting Intern

Downey Hospital (now PIH)

July 2012 - August 2013

Entering invoices with Mediclick. Maintaining an Excel sheet that tracks purchase orders and manual invoices.

Key Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Procreate
- Excel 2019
- C#
- Git
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Visual Studio
- Visual Studio Code
- Vectornator
- Sketch App
- SQL
- macOS bash
- Vue.js

Education

C# Foundation Series: Modules 1 through 9

• Certificate Module 9 Certificate (Hotel Management App)

SQL Basics

• Certificate SQL Databases: From Start to Finish Bundle

UCLA

• History BA, 2005